A.D.
M.
Due to its declining birthrate of the human popula- tion,
Akibat dari turunnya tingkat kelahiran populasi manusia,
this country has turned into a nation of cats.
negara ini menjadi negeri para kucing.
Cat Country Japan.
Negara Kucing Jepang.
Sora and Shopping Spree
Sora dan Toserba
Our fridge broke,
Kulkas kami rusak,
so we had to go to the store to buy a new one.
jadi kami harus pergi ke toserba untuk membeli yang baru.
I see, so this is a department store.
Begitu, jadi ini toserba.
They sell all sorts of things here.
Ada banyak barang dijual di sini, ya.
Dad, don't let Sora make you buy anything weird.
Ayah, jangan sampai disuruh Sora beli yang aneh-aneh.
This fish thing is quite a fine item.
Ikan ini sungguh mahakarya.
Guess we'll buy it.
Kita beli aja, yuk.
Dad is way too easy on Sora.
Ayah terlalu manja sama Sora.
A fish-smelling cushion… humans definitely hate it.
Bantal bau ikan… manusia pasti benci banget.
Fridge Corner
Pojok Kulkas
Welcome.
Selamat datang!
It's the Great Kitty Fridge Revolution.
Inilah Revolusi Kulkas Kucing!
Hmm. Great Kitty Revolution… fascinating.
Hmm. Revolusi Kucing… sangat menarik.
This incredible fridge notifies you when there are ingredients inside that kitties can eat!
Kulkas canggih ini bakal memberi tahu kalau ada makanan kucing di dalamnya!
It really is something else.
Benar-benar terobosan baru.
Oh ho ho…
Ohoho…
There is tuna inside today.
Hari ini ada tuna di dalam.
You'll never miss a chance to get a share of the delicious food.
Kamu pasti tidak bakal kelewatan makan enak!
How convenient!
Praktisnya!
Let's go with this one.
Yuk kita ambil yang ini!
Would you like to add the optional button that lets kitties open the door?
Mau tambah tombol opsional biar kucing bisa buka sendiri?
Hmm, I don't really think we need tha—
Hmm, rasanya kita tidak terlalu perlu i—
Wouldn't it be more convenient to have it?
Tapi bukannya lebih praktis kalau ada itu?
Well, no, fridges have things cats shouldn't eat in them, too…
Bukan gitu, masalahnya di kulkas ada makanan yang tidak boleh dimakan kucing.
Is it a no?
Gak boleh, ya?
Uhm, well…
Ehm, anu…
Hotori, h-how about the button…?
Hotori, tombolnya…?
We don't need it.
Tak perlu.
Hotori, how's Sora?
Hotori, Sora gimana?
He's asleep, hugging that fish cushion.
Lagi tidur, sambil meluk bantal ikan itu.
I'm glad he likes it.
Syukurlah dia suka.
It reeks fish, right?
Baunya lumayan menyengat, ya.
It sure does.
Iya, ya, amis.
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe was utilized
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe diutilisasikan
: geckyzz
: geckyzz